(Leonard:)Keep going, buddy. You're doing great.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I'm your girlfriend
and you should have taken my side.
(Amy:)That's it. End of story. Good night.
(Sheldon:)Wow, Amy's mad and Leonard was right.
(Sheldon:)What a weird day.
(Penny:)Hey, sorry this took so long.
But you used to work here.
(Penny:)- You know how it is.
- Kitchen slammed again?
(Penny:)No, I'm a terrible waitress, remember?
So anything I can do
to help you move tomorrow?
(Howard:)Now that you mention it,
I was thinking tomorrow might not be great.
- What's your excuse this time?
- No excuse.
(Howard:)It's just, you know, I'm Jewish...
(Howard:)...and technically, we're not supposed
to drive or carry anything on the Sabbath...
(Howard:)...so this one's on God.
That might be more convincing if you didn't
have a mouthful of bacon cheeseburger.
My religion's kind of loosey-goosey,
you know.
As long as you got your schmeckel
clipped and don't wear a cross, you're good.